We're the only two survivors
from our company.
We have won,
but this is the price of war.
They paid a far greater price than we did.
We killed more than
1,000 Pakistani soldiers.
It's not about them.
It's about our soldiers.
That's why I'm here.
This was neither the first war
nor the last.
But the wars to come
will not end like this.
A secret program.
To prepare the next generation
of Indian soldiers.
Soldiers who will rewrite the rules
of warfare.
I have the trial permission.
But to make sure the program stays
permanent, I need you.
Why me?
Because you know
the price of war, Guru ji.
India's most important offshore oilfield,
Mumbai High,
is in great danger.
Terrorists have attacked Mumbai High
via a sea route.
Twenty-eight ONGC workers are being
held hostage.
If we try to save them,
they've threatened to blow up
the oil rig.
The terrorists have the hostages
and the first-mover advantage.
How will you defeat them?
Come in, Charlie One.
This is Colonel Fateh Singh Lakhawat.
Team, proceed to target.
Risking such an important mission
with a new team?
Not a risk. Guts.
No guts…
no glory.
How can they breathe without
oxygen cylinders?
My soldiers can hold their breath
underwater for seven to nine minutes
without reducing their swimming speed.
Alpha One. Fourteen targets in all, sir.
Seven on deck, four in the control room,
and three on the lower level
with the hostages.
They aren't wearing night vision glasses.
How can they still see?
Dr. Cherian,
they don't need to see
because they can hear.
Their hearing ability beats
that of an ordinary person.
Come in, Charlie One. It's a go!
Go.
One shot.
One kill.
No luck.
All skill.
Bomb defused.
Hostages released, sir.
Move! To the exit!
Team terrorists, you lost!
Get up!
Chin up, guys. Chin up!
- Great job, guys.
- Well done, boys.
That was a war games exercise!
Ladies and gentlemen,
presenting Team Alpha.
The first. The fastest.
The strongest.
Reflexes matching an eagle.
Strength to floor wrestlers.
They've run in
minus 30-degree temperatures,
where most people struggle to breathe.
India's most elite and advanced
commando program.
Human lethal weapons, with Alpha
running through their veins.
- Alpha?
- Yes, Alpha.
The team was injected with the serum,
then they were trained by our very best.
Lt. Col. Vikrant Kaul.
My Guru ji.
I lost an eye in the Kargil attack,
but my vision is sharper than ever.
I trained Cobra, Ghatak
and many other teams,
but I've never seen an attack team
like Alpha.
They're bloody good.
And that's an understatement.
But according to protocol,
you should've taken clearance from DRDO.
Do you know the meaning
of top secret, madam?
"Strictly need-to-know basis."
Understand what science means,
Col. Lakhawat?
Or do you ignore it, too?
You're the one who ignored it, madam.
You didn't look carefully.
The Chief Scientist in this program
is your senior
in experience and qualification.
Doctor John Verghese.
Hello, everyone.
The Alpha serum.
It makes our tissues, muscles, and organs
stronger and more efficient.
It improves vision, hearing,
reflexes, senses, and lungs.
Improves everything.
What if a soldier is hit by a bullet?
Soldiers are not invincible.
They're human.
A headshot would kill them.
But if the wound isn't serious,
the Alpha serum can heal it.
In nature, many creatures like lizards
and lobsters can regenerate.
The Alpha serum acts on damaged organs
by mimicking that process.
The initial idea was to facilitate…
faster recovery for our soldiers.
How often must this serum be administered?
Before every mission?
Once you go Alpha,
you can't go back.
We need everyone's approval to
take this program to the next level.
Did you talk to Janaki's sister?
She was going to get a second opinion
in Spain.
Yes, I received Aruna's email.
I'm glad we found out in time.
Found out what?
I'm a bloody scientist, Preeti.
I don't believe in luck.
Not in sugar-coating either.
Just give me the facts, please.
It's confirmed.
Congenital heart disease.
During pregnancy, the mother's heart
has to work double.
Your heart can't handle it.
This is suicidal, Janaki.
It's your first trimester.
It's still possible.
You need to have an abortion.
So I can never be a mother?
We don't have a choice, Janaki.
Please.
I'm with you.
We'll face it together.
We've tried for so many years.
It's too much of a risk.
If I feared death,
I would not have married a soldier.
I listened to my heart then,
and I'll listen to it now.
My heart is weak,
but it has made a decision.
Why are you so stubborn?
Stubborn girls change the world, Vikrant.
This child has chosen us.
We're having this baby.
Promise me?
Your heart can't handle it.
My heart is weak,
but it has made a decision.
It makes our tissues, muscles, and organs
stronger and more efficient.
The Alpha serum repairs
damaged organs.
We're having this baby.
Promise me?
This is a medical miracle.
Janaki's heart is improving.
It's showing rapid improvement.
And no complications with the pregnancy.
Janaki, it's the last two months.
So take care, okay?
Thank you.
Come.
Our Alpha soldiers.
Brain hemorrhage.
Three of the six died on the spot
from a brain bleed.
The other three are in the ICU.
According to the program,
my team has been
monitoring their vitals for the past
ten months. Every day.
Their vitals were perfect.
There was no warning.
- Sir, you know why this happened, right?
- Alpha.
Move!
We're trying to save the child.
Guru ji.
Did you give the Alpha serum to Janaki?
I thought I would save her.
You didn't save her. You killed her!
Alpha is the property
of the Indian Government.
It was only tried on soldiers,
who signed up for it.
Do you understand what this means?
The Alpha serum is running
through your child's veins.
Your baby belongs to the country.
Only the country has rights
over the child, not you.
Vikrant.
I'm sorry.
We couldn't save Janaki.
Take the baby away.
Vikrant!
Vikrant! Listen to me.
They've taken your daughter.
Where's my daughter?
She's gone numb.
She's cold.
She's not breathing, Fateh.
She's dead, Guru ji.
You shouldn't have stolen the serum.
But I won't let them arrest you.
I respect soldiers like you.
I was a soldier.
I'm done.
Internal Inquiry has testified that
Alpha should have been tested
for another six months.
But you pushed it.
I did.
Nor did I ask for anyone's permission.
Six cadets are dead.
If this version of Alpha had worked,
how many cadets would've been saved?
What use is blood
if it does not spill for the nation?
A bullet didn't kill them.
Your negligence did.
Disobeying orders is not a mistake.
It's a crime.
Under normal circumstances,
the punishment is court-martial.
But considering your exemplary
career record,
this Committee has decided to take
disciplinary action instead.
We're demoting you.
You'll be demoted from Colonel
to Lt. Colonel.
You're now posted to the Cherrapunji
Special Forces base.
A place where you'll never see
the battlefield again.
And as for the Alpha program,
it has been shut down permanently.
Despite this humiliation
and this injustice,
one thing has not changed.
That I am a patriot.
A true patriot.
Mark my words.
The day will come
when you'll hold up my patriotism
as an example to the world.
You have no idea that
by shutting down Alpha today,
what a grave mistake you've made.
Not a mistake.
A sin.
Jai Hind!
I need money and men.
When can we meet?
Sir, I'm in Rajasthan,
and you're far away in Cherrapunji.
How can we work together?
I've been posted to such
an inconsequential place
where no one watches me.
Even though I'm posted in Cherrapunji,
my full focus will be on our program.
Look! Alpha's new facility.
But how?
There are some people
who understand the importance of Alpha.
Who are they, sir?
A few patriots like me.
This was their factory.
Put all your focus on Alpha.
Create a version of the serum
that can be given to every Indian soldier.
Sir, you never give up, do you?
Why would I?
Especially now that
I hold the ace in the pack.
Sir, giving Col. Kaul a stillborn baby
that belonged to someone else
and telling him it was his daughter
was wrong.
Sometimes the line between
right and wrong is blurred, Verghese.
And for me,
nothing matters more than Alpha.
What should we call her, sir?
Her mother's name was Janaki.
We'll call her…
Sita.
The baby elephant is with his family,
who protects him.
And my parents?
Where are they?
They abandoned you.
Fateh sir brought you here.
Verghese Uncle!
Verghese, is the effect
of Alpha showing?
Not yet, sir.
Happy 12th birthday, Sita!
Uncle, didn't Fateh sir come?
He's very busy.
Otherwise, he'd be here.
Wait. One minute.
This is your birthday gift.
Wow!
Soldier!
Coding and hacking.
She's excellent at both, sir.
Way beyond her age.
Her IQ is very high, sir.
We don't need her to write a book.
Tell me, has Alpha shown its effect?
It's the puberty hormone.
Alpha has finally kicked in.
Through Sita, we'll be able
to develop a new version of Alpha.
Are you crying? I see tears.
Don't cry.
People are either strong or weak.
Gender has nothing to do with it.
There are two kinds of people
in this world.
Wolves and sheep.
I'm a wolf.
What are you?
A wolf's child is a wolf, sir.
Well done!
Here's your reward.
What did you call your father?
Baba.
I got it for my first mission.
When will I get my first mission?
When you become an Indian soldier.
What's this?
Alpha.
What's Alpha?
The first letter of the Greek alphabet,
and our program's motto.
The first.
The fastest.
The strongest.
If you look closely, every city
is an urban jungle,
and in that jungle, Alpha rules.
That's why I called the serum "Alpha."
And that's what you are.
Alpha.
Sir!
Sir, it's Tel Aviv. The Mossad Chief
wants a word.
- Cancel everything. This takes priority.
- Yes, sir.
Let's get to it.
- Karan.
- Yes, sir.
- Show me.
- Sir.
Sir, five bodies were found.
The first was Subrato Das.
He was traveling alone
in the last metro.
Just one stab. Dead.
Five hours later, Amit Thakur.
He saw someone ahead,
so he honked.
The car was rigged.
Number three, Ajinkya Sethi.
A sniper kill, sir.
The bullet went through the window and
his glasses, straight into his left eye.
Next was Madhur Kulkarni.
In broad daylight, a headshot.
Fearless.
The last and most ruthless, Susan Cherian.
Suffocated to death.
Sir, they've all been murdered
in the past 48 hours.
All from different departments
and ministries.
DRDO, NSA, NSG,
Military Intelligence,
and the Ministry of Defense.
We're trying to work out the common link
that made them targets.
Alpha.
ID Sita. 14:25 hours.
Access granted.
Where were you for the last two days?
What are you eating?
Thanks.
I haven't had breakfast.
So…
Sita, what are you doing?
Good morning, Baba.
Today Sita herself has come
to burn Lanka.
Sita has gone crazy!
She's killing everyone. Find her.
Let's get her! Get the bombs!
Get the guns!
Grenade!
Hi, boys.
Where are my parents?
Happy 12th birthday, Sita!
- Uncle, didn't Fateh sir come?
- He's very busy.
I'm a wolf. What are you?
One shot.
One kill!
There's only one punishment
for a traitor.
On your 18th birthday,
what could be more special than that?
One kill!
Target in sight! Target in sight!
Sita is on the bridge.
Don't lose visual. I repeat.
Do not lose the visual.
No one will shoot!
Have you lost it?
Hands up, Sita!
Drop the gun!
Put the gun down!
Why did RandAW Chief Vikrant Kaul travel
to a remote corner of the country
to meet a forgotten soldier?
I had no choice.
Honestly, Guru ji, stay out of this.
It's in your best interest.
What are you up to, Fateh?
I've killed six.
Now just two left.
Who is she?
How did you get this?
Look carefully. You know her.
She's very close to you.
I buried my daughter
with my own two hands.
Sita.
Her name is Sita.
Sita became the Alpha soldier
we all hoped for.
She was my pride. Our very best.
Then one day she flipped.
The serum twisted her brain.
Everyone associated with the program…
she's killing them all.
Special Forces shut Alpha down
twenty years ago.
How are you running it?
Who is funding it?
I never thought you'd become a traitor!
Sita is the traitor, Guru ji.
She's killing our national assets.
Now she's after the RandAW Chief
and a Lt. Colonel.
Don't worry.
My men are looking for her.
When they find her, they'll kill her.
She's my daughter, Fateh.
How? You don't even know her.
You can't imagine how hard
it is for me to kill her.
Your daughter died twenty years ago.
Now she's my Sita.
I'll expose the truth
about you to everyone,
and you'll hang for it.
I will.
But only after Sita.
After all, she's the one murdering people.
Don't let your emotions cloud
your judgment again, Guru ji.
The last time you did that,
you lost your wife.
This time it may be your daughter.
I hate coffee.
Baba gave me the habit, Soldier.
One cup for him,
and one for me.
I'll have my last cup with him.
I'll get our revenge, Soldier.
Two lab rats have survived.
But we'll kill Baba at the very end.
Like enjoying a fine dessert
after lunch.
We'll save the best for the last.
But before that… Vikrant Kaul.
Kaul. A Kashmiri Pandit surname.
Sanskrit for "family."
He left the army 20 years ago.
Then he went totally off the grid.
After Luthra died, he was
suddenly appointed RandAW Chief.
Congratulations, Vikrant!
I love it.
Okay.
Two weeks ago, he flew from Delhi
to Madrid, from there to Valladolid.
Four days later, he came back to India
from Spain.
The same route last month.
In March too. And in December.
These RandAW guys love travelling!
He's in Spain again?
Sad.
We'll have to wait
till he's back in India.
Soldier, all his trips to Spain
were on commercial flights.
That means personal trips.
What's special about Spain, Kaul?
Girl's got style!
A firecracker
No touching
Lightning striking
Girl's a storm
Challenge her
You've had it
Acts first
Thinks later
Kohl-lined eyes
Burning through the heart
Encircles the heart
Now she's gone
Girl's chilled Champagne
Toned and maintained
Cast off the evil eye
Girl's got style!
Girl's chilled Champagne
Toned and maintained
Cast off the evil eye
Girl's got style!
Soft breeze
Wind perplexed
Sturdy form
Kickass
Challenge her
You've had it
Acts first
Thinks later
Those eyes of hers
Robs the whole village
She heeds no one
Her law is law
Sweet as honey
Melting in the mouth
Showers colors
To the world
Girl's chilled Champagne
Toned and maintained
Cast off the evil eye
Girl's got style!
Girl's chilled Champagne
Toned and maintained
Cast off the evil eye
Girl's got style!
A firecracker
No touching
Lightning striking
Girl's a storm
Challenge her
You've had it
- Cast off the evil eye
- Acts first
Girl's got style!
Vikrant, listen to me.
They've taken your daughter.
No, listen! I want to show you something.
Just come. Just come with me.
I overheard Colonel Fateh.
The Alpha serum is running
through your child's veins.
Your baby belongs to the country.
Your other daughter.
- What?
- I'm sorry, Vikrant.
Janaki knew, but she didn't tell you.
She also stopped me from telling you.
Having one baby was a risk,
and she knew you'd never let her
carry two babies.
They're twins, but not identical.
The sister, who was born first,
protected the other.
No one must know about this.
And please--
I'll delete all the records.
Thanks, Aruna, for bringing her here.
Vikrant, how will you live without her?
She's our niece.
We'll be more than happy
to have her, but…
you're her father.
I have no option, Manish.
No one must know she's my daughter.
I want her to lead a normal life.
When she's older and starts
asking questions…
I'll tell her the truth
about what happened
to her mother and sister.
Thought of a name for her?
You know Janaki loved this name…
Durga.
The destroyer of demons. Durga.
I always said you were special.
There was no one like you.
But there is someone, Durga.
She's just like you.
This is Mom, this is you,
and this is my sister.
And I'm the one behind her.
She always protected me.
Pa, did you think of a name for her?
Si…
Sita?
- Is she okay?
- She's in terrible danger.
Fateh will kill her.
Or she'll kill Fateh.
And you too.
To be honest, she should kill me.
Because I've been
a horrible father to her.
What? No, no, no.
Pa, listen to me.
You're the best father in the world.
When you got the chance,
you did your best.
What happened was not your fault.
I need your help.
We need to find her.
We have to save her at any cost.
If Sita is caught,
she'll be arrested for the murders.
As the RandAW Chief,
I can't protect her officially.
We have to do it unofficially.
Only you and me.
For Sita. For our family.
Maybe I trained you for this day.
Pa, not a day has gone by that
I haven't missed my sister, Sita.
She was born first
so she could protect me.
I've always wondered
how I'd ever repay her.
I guess this is my only chance.
Let's bring Sita home, Pa.
Let's make our family a family again.
We got him, Soldier!
Yes! Mr. Family Man
is coming back to India.
Spain Air 5837A. Madrid to Delhi,
Delhi to Srinagar.
Srinagar? Kashmir?
Why Kashmir?
Come on, Sita!
He's Kashmiri. Of course
he'd have a home in Kashmir.
Vikrant Kaul,
property registrations? Nothing.
Any other family member?
Janaki Kaul. Wife.
Boom!
Nicely done, Janaki.
Such a huge house in Betaab Valley!
Cool.
Pretty.
Was it necessary to travel separately?
It's for your own safety, kiddo.
Being careful is the new brave.
That's quite cool. Just like this house.
Wow, Pa! Ma had some great taste.
This is so beautiful!
This place has been my off-grid
personal base for years.
It's my own safe house.
The kitchen is completely stocked up.
Your favorite Italian coffee
is there too.
Coffee.
I'll get there ASAP.
Okay. See you, Pa.
- Love you.
Cool.
Sita?
Fateh sent you for me?
He has hurt my ego.
No, no, no. I'm so sorry.
I didn't know.
I'm your sister.
Sister?
Should I tie you a rakhi?
Sita.
I just want to talk to you. Please.
The rule is simple.
If you can stop me, then you get to talk.
Can we talk now?
Still wanna talk?
So you wanna sit and talk?
Okay.
You shouldn't have laughed.
Sita… that's our father.
Sita.
Papa.
Pa!
We don't look alike.
Want some?
You've gotten plenty of cardio too.
Don't eat.
I'm just loving this desi Chinese.
I…
I'm so sorry, kiddo.
"Kiddo"?
Don't get ahead of yourself, Kaul.
And you?
What nonsense were you saying?
That we're sisters?
And he's our father?
That's the truth.
Shut up!
Who is she?
My mother?
Yes. Janaki.
- Didn't she come on the family vacation?
- She died…
after giving birth to you both.
Sita…
you and I are twins.
I'm exactly like you.
Look, sis, you're good.
It's been a while since
anyone challenged me.
But exactly like me?
Who are these two boring people?
My parents.
I mean, my adoptive parents.
Adoptive parents?
How many parents does she have?
Listen to me--
She has three parents here
and one in heaven.
And what did I get?
Fateh.
What's the difference between
a guinea pig and me?
What is the difference between
a guinea pig and me, Kaul?
After a few days of experiments,
the guinea pig
is put down using sodium pentobarbital.
And me? I didn't even get that option.
Sita, Fateh lied to Pa.
Pa thought you were dead all this time.
If I'd known about you,
none of this would've happened.
I'd have come to save you.
Like you've come today?
What is it, sis?
Feeling bad for me?
Honestly, I feel bad for you.
What's this circus?
What's going on here?
Birthday.
- Which one?
- Eighteenth.
Eighteenth birthday?
Same day, right?
I wish I had a photo
from my 18th birthday.
Quite the party it was!
Happy 18th birthday, Sita.
Thank you, Baba.
Thank you for the dress
and for the dinner.
Thank you for everything.
It really means a lot to me.
Wazeer.
Arms dealer.
He's a bloody traitor.
Kill him.
And then you'll see what
a soldier's life is all about.
So all this wasn't for my birthday?
On your 18th birthday,
you're going to undertake your
first mission for the country.
What could be more special than that?
Take off your clothes and come.
Join the party.
Happy birthday!
That was the first time.
My first kill.
After that, Fateh kept giving me targets,
and I kept killing them.
Fateh got his Alpha soldier,
and I got my life's purpose.
Then one day, everything changed.
Next target. John Verghese.
Stay sharp, or you're dead.
Baba, how can I kill Dr. Verghese?
Verghese is a traitor.
He betrayed the country.
And there's only one punishment
for a traitor.
There's only one punishment for a traitor.
Death.
There's only one punishment for a traitor!
For me, Baba's words were always
set in stone.
Yes.
But for the first time,
I couldn't shoot.
I was waiting for you, Sita.
Before dying,
I wanted to tell you something.
And then Uncle Verghese told me
the story of my life.
And Alpha's.
Have you ever thought about Alpha?
Why aren't there more soldiers like you?
Because everyone who was given
the Alpha serum has died,
except you.
Fateh has only one purpose in life.
To find out how more soldiers
like you could be created.
You might remember that I collected
your blood samples every week
to try and understand how you were
the only survivor.
Why the serum hadn't killed you,
and whether I could make a new version
of Alpha from your blood?
But we didn't have cadets to test it on.
So, Fateh had to find new subjects.
Ordinary, innocent people
became the new test subjects…
but none of the poor souls survived.
Then we found this old graveyard.
Fateh filled every grave here.
And he's ready to fill one last grave…
but I can't let that happen.
What do you mean?
The new version of Alpha
will not fail, Sita.
What are you hiding?
A few days ago,
Fateh found my research
on the new version of Alpha.
Verghese, you turned out to be weak.
Spending time with Sita
has made you emotional.
How dare you hide this from me?
We can't do this.
We cannot harvest the serum
from Sita's brain cells.
The poor girl will remain
in a medical coma for life.
She'll become a living corpse.
You can't do this, sir.
Sita will be sentenced
to a living death, sir.
Verghese…
bravery demands sacrifice.
Baba.
Fateh is ready to kill me?
He didn't just stop there.
After he found the research,
a man came to meet him.
The new version of Alpha.
Congratulations!
There's no stopping Operation Odyssey now.
I have no idea what Operation Odyssey is.
I was scared.
That's why I ran away from the lab.
I tried to warn a few people
about Fateh's evil plans.
They were the same people who approved
the Alpha program twenty years ago.
Fateh claimed they were all traitors.
They weren't traitors.
The real traitor is Fateh.
Fateh's mission must be stopped, Sita.
He's a threat to you.
The secret behind the Alpha serum
lies within you.
So, my dear…
run away.
Far from the facility.
A new team of doctors and surgeons
is coming for the procedure.
- Don't go there.
- Let them come.
This procedure, the new Alpha program,
can only exist if the facility exists.
If Fateh exists.
Sita.
There's a man in that photo,
RandAW Chief Vikrant Kaul.
Go meet him.
He has a story to tell you.
Uncle, no!
Verghese Uncle wanted me to meet you.
Now I know why.
He believed we'd have
a happy family reunion.
But we only have one thing in common.
Our stupidity.
We fell straight into Fateh's trap.
I came here to talk to you,
not to kill you.
You guys are free to go.
Where are you going?
I'm going for Fateh.
Don't follow me.
No.
You're not.
You two will stay here.
Safe and secure.
I'll deal with him. Durga.
Back off, Kaul.
Don't play the father.
I've tried the family scene with Fateh.
It's not for me.
Before I change my mind
and blow your brains out,
go.
I'm not going anywhere.
I lost my daughter once.
I can't lose her again.
You already have a daughter, Kaul.
You celebrate her birthdays,
you celebrate every silly thing
about her life.
I mean nothing to you.
But if you're still finding it hard,
just believe what you've believed
for all these years.
That this daughter of yours
died at birth.
Okay?
Guys!
Heavy boots. All around us.
They're armed.
Rifles.
Fateh followed me.
Found Sita?
Yes, sir. A bike was found
outside the house.
I confirm that both
Kaul and Sita are inside.
Sita mustn't be harmed.
I want her alive.
And Kaul, sir?
Find Sita, then kill him.
Copy that, sir.
Don't take Fateh lightly, Sita.
He's the lion of his jungle.
Lions only pretend to be ferocious.
It's the lioness who goes for the kill.
And don't forget, my name is Sita!
Let the trial of fire begin!
Sniper, take the shot!
RandAW Chief.
My armory. Come, let's move.
Tools out!
Cutters, pluckers, hammers!
Come on! Break in!
Move in! Move in!
Both of you, leave.
There's a door that leads to the forest.
Come on, girls. Now!
I don't run away
from the battlefield, Kaul.
This is not running.
It's called a strategic retreat.
Sometimes stepping back
is moving forward in war.
And right now, there's a whole army
out there.
How many? Twenty? Thirty?
- Listen…
- It's not your cup of tea…
- Listen to me.
- but this is what Fateh trained me for.
And I trained him!
Sita, I know it's hard,
but right now you have to trust Pa.
How can I trust anyone?
Put yourself in my shoes.
That's what I've done since
I was a kid.
When I found out you were still alive,
I've often wondered what if it was…
me.
If I was born a few seconds
before you on that day,
what would've happened?
I would've been raised in a lab,
and you would have had a normal life
in Spain.
But, Sita,
you protected me.
Please give Pa a chance
to protect you today.
Prepare for entry.
We're running out of time.
Give me 72 hours.
You want Fateh, right?
I'll bring him to you.
I promise you that.
Okay.
This phone has the coordinates
of a safe house.
Avoid highways and check posts.
Any more basic advice?
Yes. The most basic of all.
Take care of each other.
Let's go.
The door?
Sir, Kaul is dead. We've found Sita.
Awaiting your instructions.
I'm coming to Kashmir to see Sita.
I'll send you the location.
Bring her there.
This is Kaul.
I'll need a few more days before
returning to headquarters.
I'm away on a personal matter.
But I've found something.
Only one word. Odyssey.
Get me any intel you have on it
from the last 20 years.
I want it in my inbox within four hours.
Stop staring and sleep.
You need at least six hours of sleep.
Or else, your brain will start producing
excess cortisol.
And then, you'll lose focus
and spoil my mood.
No way! You have insomnia too?
Too?
Look, apart from Alpha, there's nothing
in common between us.
Do you always put on this tough-girl act?
You must feel some emotion.
Like deep inside.
If you only feel good when you're
killing someone,
something deep inside you dies.
This tough-girl act isn't an act.
If you were with me,
you would have understood.
I am with you now.
You can trust me, you know.
If I said I trusted you,
would you let me sleep?
Of course! I'll sing you a lullaby too!
Should I?
- Please keep an arm's distance.
- Okay. Easy.
- Breathe in.
- Move back!
Breathe out.
Do you mind takin' me
For a spin around, eh?
Wanna check out if you're in the vibe, eh
She be rollin' like a movie star bae
- We in this together ride or die, eh
- Nothing to fear with you here
With you by my side
I'll stop the storm
Let me have my way
Your way is good too
Let us take a leap of faith
O friend, now I've found you
This world will dance on my fingertips
O friend, for sure
I'll make the sky fall to the ground
Do you mind takin' me
For a spin around, eh?
Wanna check out if you're in the vibe, eh
She be rollin' like a movie star bae
We in this together ride or die, eh
Do you mind takin' me
For a spin around, eh?
Wanna check out if you're in the vibe, eh
She be rollin' like a movie star bae
We in this together ride or die, eh
Now that I've found you
All sorrows are disappearing
All the small joys of life
All so clear to me now
There's nothing we can't do
Things that no one could imagine
We overcame the challenges through love
No one can stop us now
The world can work wonders
And so can we
With you by my side
We'll make the river part
Nothing to fear with you here
With you by my side
I'll stop the storm
Let me have my way
Your way is good too
Let us take a leap of faith
O friend, now I've found you
This world will dance on my fingertips
O friend, for sure
I'll make the sky fall to the ground
Do you mind takin' me
For a spin around, eh?
Wanna check out if you're in the vibe, eh
She be rollin' like a movie star bae
We in this together ride or die, eh
Tired of talking non-stop?
Eat!
No more breaks till the safe house.
Kashmiri apple. Pa's favorite.
Listen, don't worry too much.
Kaul is damn tough.
I've read his file.
He can look after himself.
Nothing scares you, right?
Fear affects only those
who have something to lose.
Someone or something you love.
So…
Ma's ring.
You know Ma was a scientist, right?
Like super smart, super headstrong.
Apparently, she could beat Pa
at chess and arm wrestling.
Deadly chick! Just like you.
Keep it.
Now you have something that's yours.
Don't lose it, okay?
No thanks.
- Why did you throw it away?
- Why did you give it to me?
I felt like it.
I thought you'd value it!
It was Ma's!
I thought it'd be important
for both of us.
For you!
Janaki is just a name to me. Okay?
Sita, you were just a name
to me as well, okay?
Stop with this "I don't care,
I'm such a cool bitch" attitude!
Because it's really getting tiring now.
What are you so upset about?
That you grew up without Ma?
Well, guess what?
That's another thing we have in common.
Sometimes, doing things to make
others happy matters the most.
- Bitch!
- Yeah, same to you!
Give me the ring.
Say sorry first.
Don't bore me. Before I change
my mind, just give it.
Hands up! Put the gun down.
RandAW Chief Vikrant Kaul is safe.
Target Fateh Singh Lakhawat in sight.
All clear, over!
Where is Sita?
How could you do this to a child?
She's not a child.
She's a murderer.
You forced her to commit the murders
for Operation Odyssey.
What is Operation Odyssey?
How are you going to use Alpha?
Where is Sita, Guru ji?
You'll start talking
when you're interrogated.
I'm taking you in.
You have no option, Fateh.
I do, Guru ji.
Where is Sita?
This doesn't look like a safe house
from any angle.
Sita? Durga?
He's waiting for you.
"He?"
The Dalai Lama is Kaul's friend?
He's gonna save us?
Namaste! Monk?
What…
Monk ji, our dad, Vikrant Kaul,
sent us to you.
You completed a 75-hour journey
in 66 hours.
Kaul was right. You two are special.
Come.
Join me, please.
Yeah, of course.
Come.
Sorry, this is my first time
making a rangoli.
This is not a rangoli.
It's a mandala.
In Buddhism, it's considered sacred.
It's actually so fascinating.
Sometimes, making a perfect mandala
takes years.
Amazing.
And once it's completed,
the monks destroy it.
Then they restart.
They begin again.
Okay!
Did Kaul send us here
for a painting class?
Let's go.
Shall we go?
This sage will get us killed.
Let's go.
Sita!
The angry one!
There was a time when…
I was dangerous too, just like you.
In life, there comes a time
when you must abandon outer noise
for inner peace.
It's amazing…
The noise outside is seeping in.
Don't worry, Monk ji.
We'll keep you safe. Okay?
Wanna die?
No, right? So kill.
I'll kill him! Stop!
I'm telling you, I'll kill him!
Kabir!
It's Kabir!
Run! It's Kabir!
- It's Kabir!
- Run!
Wait a minute.
Are you Kabir? The Kabir?
Who "the Kabir?"
Pa has told me so much about him.
This guy's no sage, he's savage!
Come on, Kabir!
Time to begin again.
Durga.
Alright. You two, back door.
Khumjung Village. Jethi Amma.
She'll take care of everything.
Okay.
Drink it.
The wound's deep.
I've given you Kabir's special medicine
for the pain.
You won't need it after this.
In twenty minutes, full recovery.
Now rest.
- Hello.
- Greetings.
Don't worry.
Kaul is alive.
But for how long?
That's your decision, Sita.
Come, save him.
I haven't seen you for so long.
Come. I'm dying to meet you, Soldier.
I'm going.
Come, let's go. Where to?
You're not going anywhere.
See the state you're in.
What do you mean? No way!
What did Kaul say?
Sometimes, stepping back
is moving forward.
You're an Alpha.
You'll get better soon.
Trust me, you'll be okay.
You'll be okay, right?
Sita,
promise me Pa won't come to any harm.
- Shit!
- That's a switch mine.
Don't move.
Sita…
throw your gun away.
No.
She came to avenge her father…
but her emotions got the better of her,
and she forgot her training.
I'm your problem.
And I'm here.
Let him go.
Fateh…
don't you dare touch my daughter!
What do you want?
What do I want?
Alpha.
Why do I want it?
What will I do with it?
You two must have a lot of questions.
You're so close to me.
You have every right…
to know the truth.
To know the truth about Odyssey.
Guru ji, you used to say I was
the perfect example of a true patriot.
I still am.
No one is a greater patriot than I am.
The only question is…
a patriot of which country?
Whose is this?
The first Pakistani soldier I killed.
The first Pakistani soldier
you killed was…
That was me!
There's a creek between
Karachi and Kutch.
Because of the high tide,
no one could see the border,
but I saw a way to enter India.
26/11 was not the first time
we crossed the waters.
I was the first one.
ISI ordered me to go to Haryana.
That was my first strike in India.
An entire family died,
except for one boy.
His name was Fateh Singh Lakhawat.
I finished him off
and found my new identity.
I learned to master the local accent.
I had been fully trained in Pakistan and
met the needs of India's Special Forces.
I was posted in Kashmir.
And then started the first phase.
I passed intel to Pakistan through
different ways and methods.
Then came phase two.
Winning the trust of the Special Forces.
For that, ISI helped
by giving me information
about terrorists operating in India.
I regretted killing my own people.
But bravery demands sacrifice.
Thanks to their sacrifice,
I got promoted.
This is the essence of Operation Odyssey.
Now for its last phase.
Being a colonel, I had access to
information that I never had before.
The time had come to attack.
Guru ji…
I'm sure you remember
Poonch, Kupwara,
and many other places, where we brutally
killed the Special Forces.
Despite this, we were badly
defeated in 1999.
We killed more than
1,000 Pakistani soldiers.
That's when ISI provided me with
the most important intel of my life.
An Indian scientist was developing
a program for the Special Forces.
Alpha!
I met him, made friends with him.
If a war hero like you backs the program,
then Special Forces will take it forward.
I'll get you the trial permission.
And when the time was right,
I used you too, Guru ji.
My Guru ji.
They're bloody good.
And that's an understatement.
ISI knew
if India successfully
created the Alpha serum,
then their army could never be defeated.
And that became my important mission.
To take the Alpha serum to Pakistan
at any cost.
But my obsession made me hasty.
Alpha should have been tested
for another six months.
But you still pushed it.
It has been shut down permanently.
Jai Hind!
I couldn't just give up.
I need money and men.
We trust you.
You'll have both.
But how will you do it?
Sita, you were the ace in my pack.
All your missions were not for India…
but for me.
For Pakistan.
I'll kill myself,
but I won't let your dream of Alpha
come true.
You don't need to fulfill my dream.
She will.
Body cam. I was getting a direct feed.
When I saw that girl fight
alongside you,
my head went into a spin.
I followed you.
You left. Night fell.
That's when I found her.
We three are soldiers,
but a war has only one winner.
Sita, I will pray for you,
but this is the cost of war.
And yes, it's not Fateh.
It's Major Zarrar Khan.
68th Falcon Regiment, Pakistan.
Sita.
- Exhaust fans!
- What?
Mine trap!
You need a counterweight.
What the hell is going on?
Bino.
Lt. Col. Fateh Singh Lakhawat
has sanctioned their entry, Captain.
What's all this medical equipment?
What's going on?
Sir, some men are carrying weapons too,
and they're not issued by Special Forces.
Come on, guys.
Where is Colonel Lakhawat?
Yes, Captain Rawat?
One question, sir.
Who are these people?
They don't look like our soldiers,
but they're still armed.
Are you questioning my authority,
Captain?
You're our senior, sir.
Following your orders is our duty.
But above all, our loyalty
lies with our country.
Well, then you leave me with no choice.
Surround them.
Keep moving.
The Cherrapunji Special Forces base
is now under our control.
Congratulations!
We never thought Operation Odyssey
would succeed.
But you made it!
Our team is ready to extract you
at the Myanmar border.
I must extract Alpha first.
Only then will I come home.
The preparation for the procedure
has started.
I know what I'm doing.
I've seen Sita fight.
When we have a thousand soldiers like her,
what do you think the outcome
of that war will be?
Victory will be ours.
I want the operation done ASAP.
We've just gotten a blood sample.
The results should take a few hours
to process.
In the meantime, let me set up
the operation theater.
You must know that…
any demon who harmed Sita
and Durga, even in the slightest,
died a horrifying death.
And here you are,
challenging both of them?
I cannot challenge Sita now.
She won't be coming.
Neither will Kaul.
Their chapter is closed.
Now, there's only you and me.
If there's an investigation, they'll
only find Sita and Kaul's dead bodies.
Everything else is clear.
I've reached the Srinagar airbase.
Copy. I'll inform Major Zarrar.
Let's go.
Where is he?
Cheetah X24, we see you.
Landing codes, please.
436522.
I repeat, 436522.
Give them landing permission.
Landing permission granted.
That wasn't the landing code!
It was the enemy code!
Jump as soon as we hit the tree line.
Send two teams to the forest.
This time, I want to see their corpses.
Go! Go! Go!
Secure the exits!
- Get ready. We're bringing her in.
- Yes, sir.
Sir, the first jeep is coming back.
Move! Move! Move!
Shoot the driver!
All units, fall back!
Keep moving! Keep moving!
They have no ammunition left!
Keep moving!
Enter from the east side.
Glory to our nation!
Glory to Mother India!
Pa, you're losing too much blood.
Sita, go.
Let's go, Pa!
You were a Pakistani soldier!
I used to call you "Baba."
This is war, Sita.
Which rule of war gave you the right
to snatch my childhood from me?
Wars have no rules,
but they come at a price.
A child paid that price,
but today, a soldier will take
revenge from you.
You cannot defeat me.
I have taught you everything.
And that will be your biggest mistake.
Today, I am not your Alpha.
I am India's Alpha!
You've become weak.
We'll kill these Indian soldiers
with their own tanks.
Sir, the target is to your left.
Fateh.
People like you have only one end.
You cannot kill me, Kaul.
I'm not an ordinary soldier
like the others.
What happens to me will not
be decided by you,
but by people who have way more
authority than you.
Pakistan…
will never admit that
I am their spy.
And India…
will not be able to break me.
You'll get exhausted
torturing me in jail.
So you…
follow your protocol
and arrest me.
You are right.
If I kill you, I'll be answerable to many.
But she won't be.
For your family.
For yourself.
For India.
I want to be India's best soldier.
There's only one punishment
for a traitor.
Baba.
This was Janaki's favorite place.
Beautiful, isn't it?
You two are just like your mother.
Stubborn girls who can change the world.
I want both of you to disappear.
Durga, you have a life in Spain.
Go back there.
And Sita,
the life that was taken from you…
here's your chance to rebuild it.
That's what I want for both of you…
as your dad.
But I'm not just your dad.
I'm also RandAW Chief Vikrant Kaul.
That's why I have a job offer
for both of you.
Join me and my team?
Tiger, Pathaan, Kabir.
And with the best boss in the world…
India.
This is the big girls' club.
If you wanna play…
Fall in line, little boy.
'Cause you can't run away.
There's nowhere to hide.
There's nowhere to go.
I've shattered the ceiling,
there's blood on the floor.
A fight to the finish,
or a kiss goodbye.
Get your last wish, baby,
'cause you're gonna die.